nnjidi.info 2015-04-09

# nnjidi.info | Privacy and TOS | Best Niche Content | Madia Magazine Publication

Privacy 

NNJIDI.INFO does not sell or rent personal information to third parties. We may also share your information for law enforcement purposes or as a result of corporate reorganization. 

NNJIDI.INFO maintains reasonable safeguards in an effort to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personal information we collect. We also have reasonable procedures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. But, despite our best efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable. 

NNJIDI.INFO will collect personal information from visitors under the age of 13 if it is submitted in connection with website account registration and with a parent or legal guardian's prior verifiable consent. 

NNJIDI.INFO will collect personal information from visitors under the age of 13 if it is submitted in connection with our registration process and with a parent or legal guardian's prior verifiable consent. To determine who is younger than 13 years old and whether parental consent is required, we ask users who wish to register to submit their date of birth. Users that indicate they are under 13 are directed to our Parent/Guardian Permission Form. 

If given verifiable permission from a parent or legal guardian, NNJIDI.INFO will collect and store the following types of personal information about a child under 13: child's name, child's e-mail address, child's mailing address, child's cell phone number {to receive text messaging}, parent's name, parent's mailing address, parent's phone number, and parent's e-mail address. NNJIDI.INFO will also collect the child's date of birth and link it to the child's personal information after obtaining consent. NNJIDI.INFO will only collect this information if it is voluntarily submitted to us by the child or parent and provided with the parent's verifiable permission. When providing consent, parents have the ability to choose which activities their children may participate in. 

We do not collect personal information about a child through the use of passive collection mechanisms such as cookies; however, information contained in a cookie may be linked to a child's personal information. For more information on how we use cookies and other information collection tools, please see our section on cookies, IP addresses and web beacons. 

We encourage parents to create a parent/child relationship on websites powered by NNJIDI.INFO's software. Once a child's registration is collected with parental permission, the child's information will be used to provide the child the benefits that come with registration. These benefits may include participation in surveys, community features {such as chat rooms and message boards}, and other site activities and features {e.g., submitting game reviews and uploading graphics}. With a parent's permission, we may also use a child's information to send the child messages {via e-mail, regular mail, or text messaging} from NNJIDI.INFO or on behalf of our partners. 

Please note that we are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity - like registration - on the child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. This means that when children participate in our online activities, they are not required to volunteer or provide more personal information about themselves than is necessary to participate in the activity. For example, if the activity only requires name, age, mailing address, and email address to participate, we would not require, as a condition of participation, that the child also provide the name of his or her grade school, favorite TV show, or other related information. 

In some instances, certain portions of our site may allow children under 13 to submit personal information such as their e-mail address without first obtaining their parents' consent. Such portions of our site operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent.
